{
    "subject": "resource/Summer_of_'42",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "United States",
    "human_readable": "The country of Summer of '42 is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7283601760864258,
            "question": "In which nation does the story of 'Summer of '42' unfold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7219918966293335,
            "question": "What country is the film 'Summer of '42' associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6547626256942749,
            "question": "Could 'Summer of '42' be considered an American film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6309328079223633,
            "question": "What is the nationality of the characters in 'Summer of '42'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5788246989250183,
            "question": "How does the country influence the overall mood or tone of 'Summer of '42'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5192315578460693,
            "question": "Is there a connection between the setting and the plot of 'Summer of '42'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4964279532432556,
            "question": "Is 'Summer of '42' a foreign film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47752439975738525,
            "question": "Does the film 'Summer of '42' explore themes related to a specific country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38281676173210144,
            "question": "Where was the movie 'Summer of '42' set?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2868688404560089,
            "question": "What cultural elements are present in the film 'Summer of '42' due to its setting?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The country of Summer of '42 is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5727_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was the movie 'Summer of '42' set?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5727_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the film 'Summer of '42' explore themes related to a specific country?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5727_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Summer of '42' a foreign film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5727_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5727_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5727_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5727_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5727_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5727_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5727_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5727_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5727_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5727_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5727_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text states the film takes place on Nantucket Island, which is part of Massachusetts, not the United States as a whole. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the film \"Summer of '42,\" which was set during World War II and filmed in locations within the United States (specifically, Fort Bragg and Mendocino in California). This supports the statement that the country of origin for \"Summer of '42\" is the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several pieces of information within the text explicitly state the film is set in New England during World War II and was filmed in Mendocino and Fort Bragg, California.  This strongly suggests a United States setting.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}